There are only two certainties in life, death and Charlie being wrong with one of his predictions.
You have to ask yourself, it's another day, does that mean Charles was wrong about something else today?
The answer is usually yes, does a bear shit in the woods? So, for a while I've been very excited
about Hollow Knight Silk Song. I am a huge fan of Hollow Knight, but I have been a bit of a
scrooge when it comes to Hopium in regards to Hollow Knight Silk Song. I have said many times,
it probably won't be coming for quite a while because there just hasn't been a peep in so long
except for a couple of tiny little tidbits, these tidily wings that they drop occasionally over
the years, but never anything substantial enough to convince me it would release. And we even had
that song in dance with Phil Spencer a couple years ago showing Hollow Knight Silk Song at one of
the Xbox conferences and saying that it would be out within a year. While a year went by and it
didn't come out, it just petered out once again, never arrived. This year, there was more hype and a
lot of hoopla about Hollow Knight Silk Song coming out in 2025 and I just didn't put a lot of stock
in it. I just didn't believe in it. I'd been hurt before. We've already been through this song
in dance when it comes to Silk Song, so I kept saying probably not and don't get your hopes up.
Well, turns out I was wrong. It is definitively confirmed to come out this year. Team Cherry even
has a tweet announcing a special presentation on Thursday for it, which I am beyond excited for.
And today at Gamescom, Jeff Keely confidently stated that it will be out this year and even show
an extended teaser. It is apparently even playable at Gamescom, so it is a real game that exists
and will actually come out this year. For six years, Team Cherry has been crafting Hollow Knight Silk
Song. It is highly anticipated and steam's most wish-listed game. Well, tonight, I can finally
definitively tell you that Silk Song is 100% actually launching this year.
And behind me, you're seeing some brand new Silk Song gameplay. The first extended look
since the last trailer in 2022. And starting tomorrow, you guys here at Gamescom can play a demo
at the Nintendo and Xbox booth. There you go. Silk Song is real.
Now, when it comes to my gaming predictions, I'm usually really happy to be proven wrong about them
because it typically means a game I'm looking forward to is coming out, which is, you know, Yeehaw.
Big woobie moment for me. So I'm happy that I was wrong about Silk Song not releasing this year,
though admittedly, it's not in my hands yet. Shit's not here yet. So who knows, it could go
tits up all of a sudden at the finish line. It's not 100% in the books yet. I guess we'll see.
But barring a catastrophic unforeseen circumstance, the game will release this year, which is extraordinary.
Now, I don't want to just yap solely about Hollow Knight Silk Song, albeit I definitely could,
because I really am pumped for it. I'm going to need to replay Hollow Knight again soon here for
the gaming channel. I want to blabber about a couple of other topics I've been getting asked about
a lot recently. But before diving into that spaghetti and meatballs, I would like to also talk
about something that I've been getting asked about a lot over the last few hours. So earlier today,
I posted that video announcing that Keso is an owner of Cheeky with us. It's our soap company.
We're extremely excited to have Keso on board. And a lot of people learned about Cheeky for the
first time. So some people that were really interested in trying Cheeky went to order it only to
notice that international shipping is astronomical pricing. And I want to just talk about that
briefly here. We do not set the international shipping rate. All of our soap is made here in America.
We make it in Montana. We also make some of it here ourselves in Tampa when we're testing it. But
it is manufactured in America in Montana, thus it ships from here. So we are subject to really
expensive international shipping rates for this product. That is out of our hands. And initially,
when we launched and for the first few months, we didn't even have international shipping turned on
because it is so expensive. You literally pay more for the shipping of our soap than you do the
actual product. But we turn it on by popular demand for people saying they don't care. They just
really want to try the soap. Doesn't matter the shipping costs. So we turn it on as an option for
them. But we recognize how crazy the price is. That is not us. We are not trying to hose you down
with international shipping rates for our benefit. Trust me, if we could, we would get it much
lower. And hopefully in the future, as cheeky grows, we will be able to have warehouses internationally
that we can ship inventory to. So it will ship from there to you. Thus it wouldn't have that huge
international shipping price attached to it. But I wanted to mention that because I know a lot of
people were really shocked by that and a little confused on why that's the case. Trust us, we know
it's frustrating for us as well. And we'd love to get that down in the future. But at our current
size, it's just not feasible for us to open up warehouses overseas. But hopefully in the future.
So now the next thing I wanted to talk about is a movie review I didn't do. I have still been seeing
a lot of movies that I haven't been reviewing and one of them was Nobody 2. I haven't heard a lot
of buzz about the film in general. But on stream, I've been getting asked a few times about like,
why am I not reviewing Nobody 2? Because I've talked about seeing it and I said it was fine. I liked it.
And people were like, well, what the fuck? Why didn't you review it? This is ridiculous.
Sometimes there's movies I'll see that I just really don't feel like reviewing and Nobody 2 is one
of them. I really like the first Nobody movie and the sequel here is fine. It's very clearly a cash
grab off of Nobody. Like that was a movie that kind of, I don't know, I wouldn't say it was like a
huge breakout success that everybody talks about, everyone knows about it. It wasn't like John Wick where
it just blew up and spawned a whole franchise. But Nobody is a film that a lot of people are familiar
with, really appreciated. So now they came back around here looking for what I consider would be an
easy payday of just making a sequel. It doesn't really have a whole lot that it wants to say.
It does kind of jump the shark a bit as well. But it is fun. Like it's a silly fun action movie
Bob Odenkirk back in the saddle again going on vacation with his family, the plumberville, and they
end up uncovering a huge drug operation and he ends up killing a bunch of people, his family killed
some people too. Like it's a good time but it's nothing special. It's like the most popcorn flick
and then when you leave the theater you'll think about it maybe a couple times and then it'll just
kind of fade out. It's not as good as the first one. It doesn't really even try to be. It's content
just being like a fun ride for like an hour and a half. I just don't have a whole lot to say about
it. That's it. Like that's the only reason I didn't review it. But like if you just want to see
an action movie you probably won't be disappointed moving on to the next thing resident evil.
So I've been doing a resident evil marathon for like a month and a half now playing all 30 resident
evil games and a lot of people have been asking am I going to be doing a tier list or a ranking when
I'm all done and also how many do I have left. I've been getting asked this a lot. So yes I will be
doing a ranking of every resident evil game from worst to best like the definitively most
donksh it to the absolute goaded resident evil game. I have currently done 24 resident evil games
so I'm almost finished. Tonight I'll be finishing resident evil 5 on stream with Matt. Then it's
revelations 2 then 6 then 7 then 8 then mercenaries 3d and then finally degeneration. But degeneration I
am having the hardest time setting up because it's an engage game. If you remember the fucking
engage from back in the day. The emulator is such a bitch to get going. I cannot get that to work
so I think I'm just going to skip it. This is me making an announcement that I'm probably just
skipping the generation. It is a throwaway title anyway. I tried I even reached out to
Bachba soup about it and when he he tried to get it working on his and again because he had
had it working at one point it no longer works now. It is a huge headache to set up. It is really
not worth the struggle so I'm probably just going to cut that one. So yeah I wanted to let you
know that right now. But to answer the main question yes I will be ranking them all and I'm very
excited to do that. I've been having an extreme amount of fun playing through every resident evil
game and I plan on doing more of these marathons for other franchises going forward. I don't know
if there's any other franchises like resident evil where it'll be this many games fucking 30 games
but I'm certainly open to it. But final fantasy was the other one I was thinking about but I don't
know if those are fun to stream. So I'll probably do final fantasy like over a long period of time
off stream for the gaming channel. Now the next topic I think I'll just go ahead and close out
the video with because it's a very big topic and it's one I've already talked about quite a bit
but it continues to just snowball. Roblox and everything happening with Roblox. I have been
keeping up with it. I've been keeping my finger on the pulse of everything in regards to Roblox
because there are so many problems with it that Roblox themselves have done a horrible job at
addressing. I know Chris Hansen is investigating them. I know there's lawsuits against them. I know
that there is like actual politicians involved now in investigating Roblox and still amidst all
that Roblox continues to make some bafflingly fucking terrible decisions and I cannot stress enough
how weird it is that Roblox keeps trying to normalize 17 plus when it comes to like dating
site and virtual sex games. Like when all of this was blowing up Roblox once again made like this wave
of bands and whatever but there were some virtual sex games still on Roblox that they said would
only be accessible to 17 plus users. Roblox 17 is still a minor. It's so weird that they don't get
that. It's so weird and it's also just weird to have sex games and Roblox in the first place. It
is a gaming platform used predominantly by children. Like it's so fucking odd. Like everything that
this company is doing and I am keeping up with it but I'm not making a video on every single new
development with it and I just wanted to let you all know that I am still actively following it
and I probably will follow up with another video on Roblox as everything continues to develop with
it. This shit is crazy but I just wanted to make a mention of that briefly. Anyway that's really
about it. See ya.